I'm sorry.
Who are you?
The sorcerer who erected the barrier here.
This spot has been chosen.
For people to kill each other in.
Unfortunately, there's
no real honor in it.
Kill each other?
Could you possibly find another
neighborhood to do that in please?
I didn't realize you were
such a funny kid there's
an old execution site
not too far from here.
It serves as the center of the barrier
it covers a five or six kilometer radius.
I went through great pains to create
this barrier so I can't impose
restrictions that are too
Unreasonable anyone who was inside the
barrier when I created it has the
right to leave it if They want but
just once if you wish right now you
could wake up outside the barrier
Would you like to do that wake up
outside the barrier is this a dream?
The space between dreams
and reality is a curse.
So be careful. Easy. Take it slowly.
The most impatient ones are
already outside waiting.
Oh, right.
I nearly forgot to tell you this.
Thank you for being friends with my son.
I appreciate it.
Sasaki! Sasaki! Sasaki!
Iiguchi!
I'm so glad to see someone I know.
Where are we?
Somewhere between Grade
and Hiroshi Street.
Never mind that.
Look, what's your opinion?
As an occult club member.
Wow.
Can I tell you about a dream I had?
We all had it.
A guy with long hair and a kasaya, right?
Yeah.
Did he also thank you for
being friends with his son?
No, that's the first
time I heard about that.
Itadori?
See our 좋아 and see our lives.
They are bright and things.
My love lives only.
If your passion remains!
This brings you.
Let's see this!
Gelect bias.
And it brings us a bit. We are weary.
In fact apologies.
Hope your love?
. . . . .
High Tension.
Yerlo-la.
Love me Love me.
Love me Help me.
Chame it Chame it.
Yeah, I call ice for fun in my death?
Bambas won no yore shuaiyo.
Sarabama da haimashou.
known i'm sorry for not
telling you sooner but
it's true it's all right
though itadori it wasn't.
in shibuya he fought
with the higher-ups after
that well that doesn't
make it any better you.
know i mean after all the
principle was like you're
yeah that's what i meant
by it's all right itadori.
but that's nice of you
well if you say you're all
right then fine there's
nothing more for us to.
Yeah.
Still, you're talking about
everyone who's ever been good to me.
I haven't been this
bummed out since I watched
Yakul get shot in the ass with an arrow.
What a nice life you've lived.
Alright then, I'm gonna help
you all stop this culling game.
Don't get me wrong though, I'm
not doing this out of sympathy.
We're cutting a deal here, understand me?
Once we clean up this
culling game for you,
it's gonna be your turn to
help me out with something.
You're trying to get in on the revisions
to the jujutsu regulations, right?
Now that the existence of
curses has gone public,
there's sure to be some
kind of revisions made.
But what exactly are you hoping for?
Whatever it is, I doubt we'll have
much trouble doing it for you.
Oh, yeah?
Get a load of sea urchin head!
What would you know about anything?
Well, I am the new head of the Zenin clan.
Oh, yeah?
Of the three crazy things I learned
today, this one's the craziest.
If I got the backing of one
of the big three families,
I could easily influence the
revisions to the regulations.
The only problem would come
later in trying to keep the
Zenin clan from getting involved
in managing the Fight Club.
Sea Urchin Head!
Name's Fushiguro. Fushiguro!
Sorry, let's be friends.
Huh? Sure.
Good.
That just leaves deciding
who's heading to which colony.
You two went to Miyagi, right?
Ding dong!
Please be advised,
effective immediately, a player has
added a new rule to the calling game.
Rule number nine, players will
know each other's information.
First names, last names,
number of points accumulated,
current colony, and number of
roles added to the game by you.
I am Kogane, a liaison between
players and the Culling Game.
Did that thing just change
personalities halfway through?
The first part was an announcement
from the Culling Game.
And now I am speaking as the personal
liaison attached to the player Yuji Itadori.
Tangan did say something about that.
This year for you?
Why is Itadori already being counted
as one of the players in the game?
Aside from those Kenjaku gave
cursed techniques and objects to,
at this point the only players should
be those who have entered a colony.
There were people whom I
had absorbed cursed objects.
The cursed objects that I distributed
are what's left of the sorcerers.
Of course, I've been secretly packed
with more than just sorcerers.
But he once existed as
an actual human being,
although it was over a thousand
years ago. Sukuna. Sukuna?
Sukuna was one of the
sorcerers that forged
a pact with Kenjaku to
become cursed objects.
I bet calling game participation
was included in their pact.
Things still aren't adding up.
You swallowed Sukuna's
finger of your own free will.
I witnessed it.
Table that.
Itadori, can you have Kogane pull
up the player's information for me?
Kogane, can you?
Sure can!
Todo!
Take a look at this guy.
So he originally had 200 points?
I wonder what he was hoping
for by adding a roll.
At the very least, he must have
killed about 40 people, right?
Whatever the reason, we
can assume it wasn't nice.
It can still help.
We could use the player's info to progress
through the culling game
without killing anyone.
Kogane, can you show me a list of
the players with 100 points or more?
Sorry, I am attached to
the player Yuji Itadori.
Oh, no, he can use you.
Just do whatever he asks.
Unless someone's in a rush
to escape the barrier,
like Tsumiki who got caught up in it.
The reincarnated
sorcerers must have forged
packs with Kenjaku for their own reasons,
so they're not necessarily
motivated to make this move.
Therefore, if there's anyone else with
an excess of 100 points like Kashimo...
That's right.
Those with 100 points and no
intention of adding a rule.
Yeah, we can lean on them.
And make them add a rule to let
Suniki escape the culling game.
Here you go.
There's another one.
All right.
First, we'll take advantage
of the Rule 8 obstacle. Huh?
Remind me what Rule 8 was again.
Then,
players who don't show a
change in points within
19 days shall be stripped
of their technique.
It's the rule that leads to death.
So we add a rule that
says it is now possible
for players to transfer
points among each other.
That way, if they keep passing
points amongst themselves,
they can avoid being stripped
of their techniques and dying.
Then we add one more.
The rule will sound something like,
if players spend enough points, it will
allow them to leave the culling game.
But that would conflict with
the rule about the continuation
of the game wouldn't it and
we find a workaround How
about we had some kind of
flexible condition to the rule
like dragging in a non-player
of the game to take their place?
That could work.
Would Kogane be making the call on that?
Either way, we know
what we need to do now.
Yeah.
Well, we're searching for the angel
to break the prison realm seal.
We'll look for Hajime Akashima.
and hunt them down.
Yeah, I'm not seeing an
angel anywhere on this list.
That's probably not her real name,
just like you're not listed as Sukuna.
Tengen said she was in eastern Tokyo.
That would mean colony number two, then.
You guys know what she looks like?
Apparently, we'll know
her when we see her.
That sounds like a load of crap.
Okay, whatever, I guess.
Panda and I will take Tokyo number
two, Fushiguro and Itadori number one?
and Kirara standby outside the barriers.
Why?
Because I said so.
What's your reasoning?
Just going by points, this
Kashimo's the strongest one,
so it makes sense for me to take him off.
It's not fair that I'm left out.
Panda, you've got a keen nose, so
focus on sniffing out the angel.
The fact that we haven't
already heard from Okotsu means
we probably can't use cell
phones inside the barriers.
so that's why we need someone keeping
tabs on what's going on outside.
Fine.
Wait a minute.
It might be better for me and Fushiguro
to split up, because if Sue can...
Shut up.
Shut up?
None of the older students
can change the roles they got.
So quit being selfish.
I'm being selfish?
I'm the one worrying about you here!
Oh man, how many times do
I have to listen to this?
It's a played excuse and a
waste of time. Yeah? Yeah!
You gonna fight or dance?
Hello, I am Kogane.
Taking place inside this
barrier is the culling game,
where players fight to the death.
Once you decide to step inside,
you too become a player.
Are you still willing to enter
and risk everything you have?
Yeah. Let's go.
On you to am I.
I keep waiting for your signal.
Uh, well, I hear you, but
there's no signal to give.
I can't do much if no one shows up. What?
That little punk.
Mouthing off to me now?
No! Please!
Look, I'm sorry, really!
If you're getting all high and mighty,
I'll pull you down.
We need to be careful of the
sorcerers who've reincarnated.
My thoughts exactly.
But just in case I've
forgotten, explain again.
Some of them are from
a thousand years ago.
Just one or two hundred years
ago, they valued life way less.
Plus, they're sorcerers.
Fighting and death are common for them.
Some may want to die fighting.
That might even be why they
forged a pact with Kenjaku.
I'll bet that Higuruma and
Kashimo are past sorcerers.
Don't expect fair negotiations.
So then other attacks
come from cursed spirits?
Especially at night.
Now, if there are modern-day sorcerers
dragged into this, like Sumiki was,
they might actually be open to
exchanging information with us.
Hello, my name is Kogane!
Taking place inside this
barrier is the culling game,
where players fight to the death.
Once you decide to step inside,
you too become a player.
Are you still willing to enter
and risk everything you have?
Yeah, let's do this.
Megumi Fushiguro has now
officially joined the Culling Game.
Would you like to see the rules first?
No need. I'm good.
Boo. Itadori.
First we have to gather
information on Higuruma.
Ready for this? Yeah.
Fushiguro's gone?
When a player enters one of
the Culling Game's barriers,
They're randomly teleported to one of nine
designated locations where
they will begin the game.
It was a rule of the barriers not included
in the general rules of the culling game.
And others were waiting in those
nine locations. Here's one.
There's a name for
players who target those
disoriented by this
unmentioned phenomenon.
Newbie Hunters
He's tougher than I thought.
That would have pulverized most guys.
But he's still kicking.
He's no ordinary person.
Darling, let's meet up, shall we?
She fell pretty easily.
I need to ask her about Higuruma.
Then I have to find Fushiguro.
Hanyu!
What the hell did you do to my woman?
Guess I can just ask him.
Oh no, Nahaba flew in.
Does that mean Hanyu was taken out?
I think I've seen that guy before.
Itadori?
Ow, that hurt!
Why did you do that to me?
I don't even know if I can stand!
Hey, you're the one who attacked me.
Damn it.
I didn't expect us to
get separated that way.
Anything?
Nui can't find him either.
This colony must be larger than Shibuya.
We're probably over two kilometers apart.
But we both know where to head.
Do you know a sorcerer named Higuruma?
You men are all alike, thinking you could
just beat a woman into listening to you,
but I'll...
Answer me.
Yes, I know him.
Could be a different Higuruma, though.
Mine has a hundred points.
That's the one. Where is he?
Hmm?
Oh, so that's how it is.
I thought I'd be in trouble with him
constantly holding higher ground,
but that propeller is
his only means of attack.
He keeps trying to get
close enough to kill me.
I need to fight him indoors.
You're about to be a smoothie!
He's turned his head towards me.
This is it!
That woman from earlier,
she was sturdy enough to smash
through buildings with me,
but a simple thrown object made her fall.
I bet their hair is the key
to their cursed techniques.
The further away from the
hair, the less sturdy they are.
How'd they become this way?
Was it part of a pact?
But no matter how tough their hair is,
it's still attached to their heads!
It got me!
Broke your fist, huh?
That's too bad.
Cause you just lost this ba - Eww!
I didn't break anything,
it's just a scratch. Ow.
I don't mind telling you
where to find Higuruma,
But I want you to do me a favor in return.
Spit it out.
Magic word.
Say please.
Or thank you. Or... Tell me.
Fine.
Will you be my knight,
please? Sure. That's fine.
Oh, you're no fun at all, are you?
I don't have time for this.
So hurry up.
I'm walking front.
Do you even know what a knight is?
My knight is supposed to protect
me with his life, if necessary.
I will, if you're telling me the truth.
Hey, wake up.
I want to ask you about a
sorcerer named Higuruma.
Itadori!
I know him.
That Higuruma guy.
You know what'll happen.
If you're lying.
I'm not like Itadori.
I'm willing to earn those
100 points on my own.
You know, I do have a name.
And that name is Remy.
It's been a while.
Do you remember me?
Who are you?
How does he know my name?
Oh, sorry.
I guess it was just me who knew about you.
I mean, you're famous after all.
Tiger of West Middle. No way.
You're from my hometown?
So you're saying you're not
a sorcerer from the past?
Why?
Do these clothes look old-fashioned?
And what's your rationale
for attacking me?
Listen, you.
A whole lot of average people who weren't
players suddenly got
let out of the colony.
But the players like me who were
in the colony from the start
have had to participate in the
calling game for 12 days already!
I'm not doing this because I want to.
Out here it's kill.
Or be killed you can get
killed while trying to
find a reason to fight 12
days out here has taught
me that i've seen plenty
of people drown in their
power so far so stop trying
to differentiate between
them as past or present
sorcerers so the sorcerers
from the past have inspired
the modern day sorcerers
to go into battle mode
in that case i gave it to
dory bad advice you sure
What about those other two?
You were allies, right?
Nah, I was just their gopher.
They would have killed me at some point.
Wait.
Enough blind following.
Tell me where we're going.
No way, pal.
What guarantee do I have you won't kill me
right after I tell you
where to find Higuruma?
Oh, I see.
It's Amai. Rin Amai.
What am I supposed to do if
you die before we get there?
That's why!
I need you to be my knight and protect me!
And use my name already just
covering my bases am i where exactly
can i find higuruma Okay fine
i'll give you a rough idea of
where we're going the stronger
people are gathered In what used
to be the heart of the city it's
where most of the supplies are
Higuruma-zen Ikebukuro
Shinjuku Got it? Got it?
I'm not afraid to be here.
It's so scary.
I'll never forget to be here.
It's not scary.
I'll be afraid to die again.
I'll forget to be back in the last night?
I'll be the same tomorrow.
I'll be the same for the rest of my life.
I'll be the same
for
the rest of my life.
I'm sorry.
But she deceived you.
I'm sorry, Itadori.
A sorcerer connected to Kenjaku?
I want to talk.
We're having a retrial.